<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MovieFlxUsingActivity</string>
    <string-array name="moviename">
        <item>Andhadhun</item>
        <item>Badhaai Ho</item>
        <item>Stree</item>
        <item>Padman</item>
        <item>Raazi</item>
        <item>Parmanu: The Story of Pokhran</item>
        <item>Sanju</item>
        <item>Soorma</item>
        <item>Raid</item>
        <item>102 Not Out</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="moviedisp">
        <item>A series of mysterious events change the life of a blind pianist who now must report a crime that was actually never witnessed by him.</item>
        <item>A man is embarrassed when he finds out his mother is pregnant.</item>
        <item>In the small town of Chanderi, the menfolk live in fear of an evil spirit named "Stree" who abducts men in the night. Based on the urban legend of "Nale Ba" that went viral in Karnataka in the 1990s.</item>
        <item>Upon realizing the extent to which women are affected by their menses, a man sets out to create a sanitary pad machine and to provide inexpensive sanitary pads to the women of rural India.</item>
        <item>A Kashmiri woman agrees to marry a Pakistani army officer in order to spy on Pakistan during the Indo-Pakistan War of 1971.</item>
        <item>A look at Indias second confidential nuclear test series at Pokhran led by Dr. APJ Abdul Kalam, during the time of PM Atal Bihari Vajpayee tenure.</item>
        <item>Sanju is a biopic of the controversial life of actor Sanjay Dutt: his film career, jail sentence and personal life.</item>
        <item>Soorma is the story of the triumph of the human spirit, about a player, who made headlines for his miraculous comeback after facing a near death experience through sheer determination, hard work and unrelenting passion for the sport.</item>
        <item>A fearless income tax officer raids the mansion of the most powerful man in Lucknow after someone mysteriously draws his attention towards the evidence.</item>
        <item>102 Not Out is a 2018 comedy-drama film, with legendary actor Amitabh Bachchan playing a 102-year-old wanting to break the oldest-man-alive record. Another Bollywood legend Rishi Kapoor plays his sad and grumpy 75-year-old son.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="moviecast">
        <item>Director: Sriram Raghavan | Stars: Ayushmann Khurrana, Tabu, Radhika Apte, Anil Dhawan</item>
        <item>Director: Amit Ravindernath Sharma | Stars: Ayushmann Khurrana, Sanya Malhotra, Neena Gupta, Gajraj Rao</item>
        <item>Director: Amar Kaushik | Stars: Rajkummar Rao, Shraddha Kapoor, Pankaj Tripathi, Aparshakti Khurana</item>
        <item>Director: R. Balki | Stars: Akshay Kumar, Radhika Apte, Sonam Kapoor, Jyoti Subhash</item>
        <item>Director: Meghna Gulzar | Stars: Alia Bhatt, Vicky Kaushal, Rajit Kapoor, Shishir Sharma</item>
        <item>Director: Abhishek Sharma | Stars: John Abraham, Boman Irani, Diana Penty, Anuja Sathe</item>
        <item>Director: Rajkumar Hirani | Stars: Ranbir Kapoor, Paresh Rawal, Manisha Koirala, Vicky Kaushal</item>
        <item>Director: Shaad Ali | Stars: Diljit Dosanjh, Taapsee Pannu, Angad Bedi, Vijay Raaz</item>
        <item>Director: Raj Kumar Gupta | Stars: Ajay Devgn, Saurabh Shukla, Ileana D Cruz, Amit Sial</item>
        <item>Director: Umesh Shukla | Stars: Amitabh Bachchan, Rishi Kapoor, Jimit Trivedi, Dharmendra Gohil</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="name">NAME</string>
</resources>
